<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nox on Claudio Jolowicz</title>
    <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/tags/nox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nox on Claudio Jolowicz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:41:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cjolowicz.github.io/tags/nox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermodern Python Chapter 6: CI/CD</title>
      <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-06-ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:41:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-06-ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Read this article on Medium
  In this sixth and last installment of the Hypermodern Python series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to discuss how to add continuous integration and delivery to your project using GitHub Actions, Poetry, and Nox.1 In the previous chapter, we discussed how to add documentation. (If you start reading here, you can also download the code for the previous chapter.)
Here are the topics covered in this chapter on Continuous Integration and Delivery:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermodern Python Chapter 5: Documentation</title>
      <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-05-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 12:49:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-05-documentation/</guid>
      <description>Read this article on Medium
  In this fifth installment of the Hypermodern Python series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to discuss how to add documentation to your project.1 In the previous chapter, we discussed how to add type annotations and type checking. (If you start reading here, you can also download the code for the previous chapter.)
Here are the topics covered in this chapter on documentation:
 Documenting code with Python docstrings Linting code documentation with flake8-docstrings Adding docstrings to Nox sessions Adding docstrings to the test suite Validating docstrings against function signatures with darglint Running documentation examples with xdoctest Creating documentation with Sphinx Writing documentation using reStructuredText Generating API documentation with autodoc  Here is a full list of the articles in this series:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermodern Python Chapter 4: Typing</title>
      <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-04-typing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:04:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-04-typing/</guid>
      <description>Read this article on Medium
  In this fourth installment of the Hypermodern Python series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to discuss how to add type annotations and type checking to your project.1 Previously, we discussed how to add linting, static analysis, and code formatting. (If you start reading here, you can also download the code for the previous chapter.)
Here are the topics covered in this chapter on Typing in Python:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermodern Python Chapter 3: Linting</title>
      <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-03-linting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 07:04:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-03-linting/</guid>
      <description>Read this article on Medium
  In this third installment of the Hypermodern Python series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to discuss how to add linting, code formatting, and static analysis to your project.1 Previously, we discussed Automated Testing. (If you start reading here, you can also download the code for the previous chapter.)
Here are the topics covered in this chapter on Linting in Python:
 Linting with Flake8 Code formatting with Black Checking imports with flake8-import-order Finding more bugs with flake8-bugbear Identifying security issues with Bandit Finding security vulnerabilities in dependencies with Safety Managing dependencies in Nox sessions with Poetry Managing Git hooks with pre-commit  Here is a full list of the articles in this series:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypermodern Python Chapter 2: Testing</title>
      <link>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-02-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 06:28:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjolowicz.github.io/posts/hypermodern-python-02-testing/</guid>
      <description>Read this article on Medium
  In this second installment of the Hypermodern Python series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to discuss how to add automated testing to your project, and how to teach the random fact generator foreign languages.1 Previously, we discussed How to set up a Python project. (If you start reading here, you can also download the code for the previous chapter.)
Here are the topics covered in this chapter on Testing in Python:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>